Guide to The Peter Dougherty Collection MSS.213
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series I: Sound recordings
  - Subseries A: Audio Works, 1976-1985
    - Roxy Music Live in London at Wembley's Empire Pool with the Sadistic Mika Band, Oct 17 & 18 1975. Recorded by P.D., October 17, 1975 - October 18, 1975; ID: 213.0264 (Box 5, Media ID: 213.0264, Case 213.0264_pt.1, Case 213.0264_pt.2)
      Side B (Oct 18th): She Sells, Strictly Confidential, Both Ends Burning, Whirlwinds, For Your Pleasure/ Diamond Head/ Wild Weekend, A Really Good Time, The 'In' Crowd, Virginia Plain
    - Slits TR3 Jan 4 '80, January 4, 1980; ID: 213.0265 (Box 5, Media ID: 213.0265)
      Side A: Newtown, Instant Hit
      Side B: Animal Space, Walkabout
    - Slits, Bradford Hotel, Boston Nov 1 '80, November 1, 1980; ID: 213.0266 (Box 5, Media ID: 213.0266)
      Content: The Type
      Side A: Tick Tock, Glass Morning, Working for Myself, All of My Dreams
    - Slits- Radio WPIX Jam/Banshees- Peel Sessions, January 1980; ID: 213.0268 (Box 5, Media ID: 213.0268)
      Content: unknown
    - Slits, Ritz Nov 2 '80, November 2, 1980; ID: 213.0269 (Box 5, Media ID: 213.0269)
      Sides A and B: Newtown, Walkabout
    - Slits, Hurrah- New Years Dec 31 1979, December 31, 1979; ID: 213.0270 (Box 5, Media ID: 213.0270)
      Sides A and B: Newtown, Instant Hit, Walkabout, Typical Girls, Man Next Door, Grapevine, Adventures
    - The Slits Aug 4 1978, Music Machine, August 4, 1978; ID: 213.0271 (Box 5, Media ID: 213.0271)
      Sides A and B: FM, Spend Spend Spend, No. 1 Enemy, New Town, Instant Hit, Femme Fatale, Love & Romance, So Tough, Shoplifting, Grapevine
    - The Slits, Hurrah Jan 30 1980, Master, January 30, 1980; ID: 213.0272 (Box 5, Media ID: 213.0272)
      Side B: Spend Spend Spend, Silence is a Rhythm Too
    - Grand Master May 28, 29 Bonds/ Slits May 31st '81 Bonds, May 28, 1981 - May 31, 1981; ID: 213.0273 (Box 5, Media ID: 213.0273)
      Sides A and B: Walkout, In the Beginning
    - Slits, My Father's Place, Nov 3 '80, November 3, 1980; ID: 213.0274 (Box 5, Media ID: 213.0274)
      Side A: Newtown, Walkabout, Man Next Door, Life on Earth, Typical Girls, Fade Away, Paint on a Face, Animal Space, In the Beginning
      Side B: Here Was Rhythm
    - Slits, East Side Club Philly July 16 '81, July 16, 1981; ID: 213.0275 (Box 5, Media ID: 213.0275)
      Container Annotation: GEER DU BOUIS 3/31/81 NORELCO- 1. "Windows that wash themselves" 2. "Shoes that grow with your feet."
    - Tom Verlaine Instrumentals for Peter D./ Television Demos '74, ID: 213.0276 (Box 5, Media ID: 213.0276)
      Side A: Tom Verlaine - Instrumentals for Peter D.
      Side B: Television '74 Demos
    - Television, Glastonbury Festival 26.6.92, June 26, 1992; ID: 213.0277 (Box 5, Media ID: 213.0277)
    - Suicide, Brixton 15.12.88, Brixton Academy, Full show!, 1988; ID: 213.0278 (Box 5, Media ID: 213.0278)
    - Shane MacGowan and the Popes, Unmastered Album - Release date 10-10-94 Details Over... ZTT, October 10, 1994; ID: 213.0279 (Box 5, Media ID: 213.0279)
      Side A: The Church of the Holy Spook, That Woman's Got Me Drinking, Song with No Name, Aisling, Handbag
      Side B: Mexican Funeral in Paris, Snake, Donegal Express, Victoria, Her Father Didn't Like Me
    - The Who Live at London's Wembly Empire Pool, October 21, 1975, ID: 213.0280 (Box 5, Media ID: 213.0280)
      Side A: I Can't Explain, Substitute, [Track Unknown]
      Side B: I'm Free --> Tommy's Holiday Camp, We're Not Gonna Take It, Summer Time Blues, Bargain, My Generation --> Join Together with the Band --> My Generation --> Maybelline, Won't Get Fooled Again
    - Bowie 1980 Floor Show, ID: 213.0281 (Box 5, Media ID: 213.0281)
    - Kraky Solo at the Lonestar Feb 2nd 1978, February 2, 1978; ID: 213.0282 (Box 5, Media ID: 213.0282)
    - Punk in London- Chelsea, X-Ray Spex, Lurkers (Lurker at Home), undated; ID: 213.0283 (Box 5, Media ID: 213.0283)
    - Punk Rock Movie by Don Letts The Screaming Target, undated; ID: 213.0284 (Box 6, Media ID: 213.0284)
      Side A: God Save the Queen, White Riot (Dancing), Generation X, Slits, Clash, Subway Sect, Alternative T.V., Boy Bust, Wayne, A.T.V., Eater, Siouxsie & the Banshees, Slits, Alternative T.V.
      Side B: Heartbreakers (2), 1977, Oh Bondage- Chinese Rock, Seventeen --> Liar, New York, God Save the Queen, J.R. in [S.A.]
    - The Blank Generation - A Shit Film by Ivan Kral/ NY Rock Party Sunday May 30th Manhattan Center, undated; ID: 213.0285 (Box 6, Media ID: 213.0285)
      Side A: Real Good Time- Patti; Little Johnny Jewel, Ame Ame Amore - Television; Loudmouth, Shock Treatment, Other Guy, Babysitter, Blitz Bop, Loudmouth- Ramones; Psycho Killer, First Week/Last Week - Talking Heads, Tuff Darts; Wayne County; Blondie; Toledo; Marbles; Shurts; Polls; Heartbreakers
      Side B: I Wanna Be Loved, Blank, Dolls, Funky But Chic, Dizzy Miss Lizzy, Talk Too Much, Peter Gun, Blondie (cut).
    - Jonathan and the Modern Lovers Live Oct. 9 1976, Town Hall NYC, October 9, 1976; ID: 213.0286 (Box 6, Media ID: 213.0286)
      Side A: Back in the U.S.A., Road Runner, RnR Leprechauns, Ice Cream Man, Ancient Ancient Long Ago, Guma Guma, Gov't Center, Martian Martians, Dodge Vegomatic, New England Springtime, Morning
      Side B: Hospital, New Teller, Important in Your Life, Time to Fly into Life's Mysteries, Abominable Snowman in the Market, Ice Cream Man, Rockin Rockin Leprechauns, Astral Plane
      Container Annotation: Jonathan Richman-Vocal, Guitar, Sax; Leroy Radcliffe-Guitar, B. Vocal; Curly-Bass, B. Vocal; D. Sharpe-Percussion
    - It's the Death, undated; ID: 213.0287 (Box 6, Media ID: 213.0287)
      Contents: unknown
    - The London Massive, undated; ID: 213.0288 (Box 6, Media ID: 213.0288)
    - Big Bout Ya 83 Stylee, undated; ID: 213.0289 (Box 6, Media ID: 213.0289)
      Currently there is no access to this title. Please contact Fales Library..
    - Don. L's Reggae 1986, ID: 213.0290 (Box 6, Media ID: 213.0290)
    - Ragamuffin Reggae 1989 Part Two, ID: 213.0291 (Box 6, Media ID: 213.0291)
    - Ragamuffin Reggae '91, 1991; ID: 213.0292 (Box 6, Media ID: 213.0292)
    - Mama Dragon, undated; ID: 213.0293 (Box 6, Media ID: 213.0293)
    - Combination, undated; ID: 213.0294 (Box 6, Media ID: 213.0294)
    - Dread at the Control, a Don Letts Tape, undated; ID: 213.0295 (Box 6, Media ID: 213.0295)
    - Rocking of the 5000, undated; ID: 213.0296 (Box 6, Media ID: 213.0296)
    - Cease '86, 1986; ID: 213.0297 (Box 6, Media ID: 213.0297)
    - Heavy Heavy Manners - A Don Dread Project, undated; ID: 213.0298 (Box 6, Media ID: 213.0298)
    - Mad Pablo Dubb[y] Connection, undated; ID: 213.0299 (Box 6, Media ID: 213.0299)
    - Wailer's Posse - Jamaican Singles, Dubs, Extended Versions. Compiled by D. Herzog 3/7/92, March 27, 1992; ID: 213.0300 (Box 6, Media ID: 213.0300)
      Contents:
      Side A: Jah Live, Smile Jamaica, Punky Reggae Party, Waiting in Vain (Dub), One Dub, Ambush (Version), Redemption Song (12"), Dubbin In, Don't Give Up, Zion Express (Bob Marley and the Wailers)
      Side B: Babylon Queendom, African (Version), Don't Space Out, Vampire (Tosh); Put it On, Black Woman (Judy Mowatt)/ Hurting Inside, Peaceful Woman; (R. Marley) Man to Man (Marcia Griffith); Bend Down Low (Martha Velez); Keep On Moving (Bob Marley)
    - Dubland, undated; ID: 213.0301 (Box 6, Media ID: 213.0301)
      Side A: Field Marshall Buckas, Hammering; Carol Kalphat, Peace Time; Tappa Zukie, She Wants a Phensic; Ray I, Good Couple; Marley, Who the Cap Fit; John Holt, Stealin Stealin
      Side B: Vivian Jackson, I Know; Dillinger/Gibbs, Hold Me Tight Out the Light; Cornell Campbell, Love is the Answer; Belmont, Reap What You Saw; Carl Malcolm, Fattie Bum Bum; Trinity, Spankin from the Ranking/Real Rankin Trinity, Fat Man Riding Section; Ray I, Weatherman Skank
    - Well Crucial '80, Peter, London '80, Black Uhuru Sensimillia [crossed out]. Clash., 1980; ID: 213.0302 (Box 6, Media ID: 213.0302)
    - The Chosen, undated; ID: 213.0303 (Box 6, Media ID: 213.0303)
    - Blue Beat Ska, Skinhead Reggae (Reggae Through Last 15 Years). A Don Letts Tape, undated; ID: 213.0304 (Box 6, Media ID: 213.0304)
    - Ragamuffin Reggae 1989 Part One, ID: 213.0305 (Box 6, Media ID: 213.0305)
    - Dread at the Control No. I, undated; ID: 213.0306 (Box 6, Media ID: 213.0306)
    - Demo Tape The Damned 22-7-70, July 22, 1970; ID: 213.0307 (Box 6, Media ID: 213.0307)
      Side A (written on cassette): See Yer Tonight, Feel the Pain, I Fall
      Container Annotation: Written by Brian James 677-1355, The Damned
    - The Damned / Johnny Moped "Starting a Moped", February 28, 1977; ID: 213.0308 (Box 6, Media ID: 213.0308)
      Side A: The Damned Live at the Roxy 28/2/77
      Side B (Johnny Moped, "Starting a Moped"): Intro, Groovy Baby, Starting a Moped, Warm Loving Bad, Wolf and Dracula, The Decision, 3-D Time, Something Else, Hell Razor, Assault & Buggery
    - Trenchtown Rock, undated; ID: 213.0309 (Box 6, Media ID: 213.0309)
      Side 1: Money Money (Inst), Get Up Stand Up. Bless the Dreadlocks, Midnight Rider
      Side 2: Sugar Dumplin, Jah Live
      Container Annotation: Thanks to Don
    - Captain Beefheart 6/11/77, June 11, 1977; ID: 213.0310 (Box 6, Media ID: 213.0310)
      Side A: Hair Pie, Suction Point, Low Yo Yo, Electricity, A Carrot is as Close a Rabbit Gets to a Diamond, China Pig, On Tomorrow, Grow Fins, Sun Zoom Spark
      Side B: Owed to Alex, Veterans Day Poppy
      Container Annotation: Jeff Moris "Whiteshoe" Tabin - guitar; Eric "Black Jew Tuckaboo" Feldman - bass, keyboard; Denny Walley - guitar; Robert Williams - drums
    - Captain Beefheart Irving Plaza December 9th 1980, December 9, 1980; ID: 213.0311 (Box 6, Media ID: 213.0311)
    - Live Captain Beefheart & Magic Band: Town Hall 2/28/73, Town Hall 10/28/72, Keystone Club 12/4/76, Avalon Ballroom '67, October 28, 1972/February 28, 1973/December 4, 1976; ID: 213.0312 (Box 6, Media ID: 213.0312)
      Side A: King Bee, Mirror Man, Black Snake Blues, Low Yo Yo Stuff, I Wanna Find a Woman…, When Big Joan Sets Up, Electricity, Click Clack, A Carrot is as Close as a Rabbit Gets to a Diamond, China Pig, Orange Claw Hammer
      Side B: Veterans Day Poppy, Old Folks Boogie, Nowadays a Woman Gotta Hit a Man, Abba Zabba, Crazy Little Thing, Sugar & Spikes, Peon, I'm Gonna Booglarize You Baby, Alice in Blunderland
    - Brides of Dr. Funkenstein Nov. 5, 78, November 5, 1978; ID: 213.0313 (Box 6, Media ID: 213.0313)
      Side A (Brides): Birdie, Ride On, Vanish in Our Sleep, Woman are Together, Disco to Go
      Side B (Funkadelic): Cholly; You Got a Thing, I Got a Thing, Everbody's Got a Thing; Cosmic Shop, Tear the Roof Off, The Sucker Medley
      Container Annotation: w/ Horny Horns, Drums - Frankie Kash Waddy, Guitar - Blackbird
    - Funkadelic Nov. 5, 1978 Palladium, November 5, 1978; ID: 213.0314 (Box 6, Media ID: 213.0314)
      Side A: Pussy, Red Hot Mamma, Into You, Standing on the Verge…; Drums, Drums.
      Side B: Maggot Brain, One Nation, Under a Groove
      Container Annotation: Vocals - Clinton, Shider, Stingray; Guitar - Hampton, Shider; Drums - Tyrone Lampkin; Bass - "Boogie," "Skeet" [Cuts], Keyboard - Bernie Worrell, W. Morrison
    - P-Funk Live MSG NYC, June 8, 1978; ID: 213.0315 (Box 6, Media ID: 213.0315)
      Side A: Cosmic Slop
      Container Annotation: Recording Date- June 8, 1978
    - US Funk Mob III, undated; ID: 213.0316 (Box 6, Media ID: 213.0316)
      Side A: Who Says Funk Band, Maggot Brain (live)
      Side B: P-Funk, Mothership Connection (Starchild), Give Up the Funk (Tear the Roof Off), Bop Gun, Flashlight
    - P-Funk II, undated; ID: 213.0317 (Box 6, Media ID: 213.0317)
      Side A: Let's Take it to the Stage, [Jammin']-Shit-Goddamn, Stuffs and Things, Chocolate City, Gamin' On Ya, Dr. Funkenstein, [Track Unknown], [Track Unknown], Move Your Sexy Body, Take Your Dead Ass Home, Stretchin' Out
      Side B: I'd Rather Be with You, Aqua Boogie, Knee Deep, Bootzilla, Hollywood Squares, One Nation, Who Says a Funk Band [crossed out], Cholly, Into You
    - Funkadelic I, undated; ID: 213.0318 (Box 6, Media ID: 213.0318)
      Side A: Can You Get to That, Hit It and Quit It, Super Stupid, Back in Our Minds, Loose Booty, Pussy, That Was My Girl, Wake Up
      Side B: Cosmic Slop, [Track Unknown], Nappy Dugout, You Can't Miss, Red Hot Mamma, Alice in My Fantasies, Sexy Ways, Standing on the Verge, Comin' Round the Mountain, If You Got Funk
    - Afrika Bambaata '81/Grand Wizard Theodore, 1981; ID: 213.0319 (Box 6, Media ID: 213.0319)
      Side A: Afrika Bambaata '81
      Side B: Grand Wizard Theodore
    - N.W.A.: Straight Outta Compton, undated; ID: 213.0320 (Box 6, Media ID: 213.0320)
      Side A: Straight Outta Compton, _ _ _ _ Tha Police, Gangsta Gangsta, If It Ain't Ruff, Parental Discretion iz Advised, 8 Ball (Remix), Something Like That
      Side B: Express Yourself, Compton's n The House (Remix), I Ain't Tha 1, Dopeman (Remix), Quiet on Tha Set, Something 2 Dance 2
      Container Annotation: ©1988 Priority Records/Ruthless Records. Commercial Release
    - REV, undated; ID: 213.0321 (Box 6, Media ID: 213.0321)
    - Beastie Boys Pass the Mic [EP], undated; ID: 213.0322 (Box 6, Media ID: 213.0322)
      Sides A and B: Pass the Mic (LP version), Jimmy James (LP version), Dub the Mic, Drunken Praying Mantiss Style, Pass the Mic pt. 2 (Skills to Pay the Bills), Jimmy James (instrumental), Netty's Girl.
    - Jumping Master, undated; ID: 213.0323 (Box 6, Media ID: 213.0323)
    - Rebel Radio, undated; ID: 213.0324 (Box 6, Media ID: 213.0324)
    - DUB CLUB BAD PARTY - Ragamuffin Style, Sambo, First Blood, undated; ID: 213.0325 (Box 6, Media ID: 213.0325)
      Container Annotation: 132 W 20 St WED NT. 1am
    - Nuf Respect to Odoc, undated; ID: 213.0326 (Box 6, Media ID: 213.0326)
    - Warrior, undated; ID: 213.0327 (Box 6, Media ID: 213.0327)
    - Reggae 86, 1986; ID: 213.0328 (Box 6, Media ID: 213.0328)
    - Ragamuffin 88, 1988; ID: 213.0329 (Box 6, Media ID: 213.0329)
    - Reggae 89, 1989; ID: 213.0330 (Box 6, Media ID: 213.0330)
    - Killer Hurts, 1982; ID: 213.0331 (Box 6, Media ID: 213.0331)
      D1on -> Rockin Well, CCC, To the Depths of Hell, '82. [image on container]
    - 51 Storm, undated; ID: 213.0332 (Box 6, Media ID: 213.0332)
    - Rankin, undated; ID: 213.0333 (Box 6, Media ID: 213.0333)
    - Dread at the Control 4, undated; ID: 213.0334 (Box 6, Media ID: 213.0334)
    - Dread at the Control 3, undated; ID: 213.0336 (Box 6, Media ID: 213.0336)
    - Stereograph Live. London '80, Peter., 1980; ID: 213.0337 (Box 6, Media ID: 213.0337)
      Side A: Sound System
    - Body Music, undated; ID: 213.0338 (Box 6, Media ID: 213.0338)
    - Revolution Sounds - Big Youth, undated; ID: 213.0339 (Box 6, Media ID: 213.0339)
      Side A (Revolution Sounds): Burning Spear - Travelin'; Fred Locks - Black Starliner
      Side B: Revolution Sounds - Big Youth
    - Bowie Interview Nov. 28, 1975, November 28, 1975; ID: 213.0340 (Box 7, Media ID: 213.0340)
      Side A: (Handwritten over printing, See Container Annotation) "Bowie Interview Nov. 28th 1975"
      Container Annotation: How Media Will Be Judged and Bought in 1975, Highlights of the 5th Annual Media Decisions Seminar. © 1975 The Martin S. Fliesler Company. Commercial Release
    - Public Image Ltd., Orpheum Theatre Boston, 1, April 18, 1980; ID: 213.0341 (Box 7, Media ID: 213.0341)
      Side A: Careering, Annalisa, Attack, Poptones, Low Life, Public Image, Death Disco
      Side B: Bad Baby, Home is Where the Heart is, Theme, Chant; Another, Public Image, Memories, Poptones
    - Public Image Ltd., NYC Palladium April 20 1980, 2, ID: 213.0342 (Box 7, Media ID: 213.0342)
      Side A: Intro, Careering, Annalisa; Attack, Low Life, Fodderstompf, Death Disco, Memories, Public Image
      Side B: Another, Poptones
    - Public Image Ltd., NYC April 22nd, 1980, Great Gildersleeves, 3, April 22, 1980; ID: 213.0343 (Box 7, Media ID: 213.0343)
      Side A: Chant, Public Image, Attack, Another, Low Life, Bad Baby, Memories, Fodderstompf, Public Image
      Side B: Careering, Annalisa, Poptunes, Chant
    - Public Image Ltd., Phil April 26, '80, April 26, 1980; ID: 213.0344 (Box 7, Media ID: 213.0344)
    - Public Image Ltd., Staten Island, undated; ID: 213.0345 (Box 7, Media ID: 213.0345)
    - Public Image Ltd., Orpheum Auditorium L.A., 9, May 4, 1980; ID: 213.0346 (Box 7, Media ID: 213.0346)
      Side A: Intro, Careering, Annalisa, Low Life, Chant, Death, Poptones
      Side B: Religion, Bad Baby, Public Image, Memories, Russia with Love
    - Public Image Ltd., San Francisco May 10th 1980, South Market Cultural Center, 10, May 10, 1980; ID: 213.0347 (Box 7, Media ID: 213.0347)
      Side A: Intro, Careering, Annalisa, Attack, Low Life, Chant, Death Disco
      Side B: Poptones
    - Palladium Check April 20th/Great Gildersleeves, April 20, [no year]; ID: 213.0348 (Box 7, Media ID: 213.0348)
    - Public Image Ltd., Brooklyn Zoo, January 29, 1983; ID: 213.0349 (Box 7, Media ID: 213.0349)
      Side A: Blue Water, Where Are You, Annalisa, Bad Baby, Careering, Religion, Home is Where…, Theme, Swan Lake, Chant
      Side B: Attack, Mad Max, Public Image, Low Life;, No Birds, Under the House
    - Sex Pistols, Anarchy in the USA, Dallas Jan 10, 1978/San Francisco Jan 14, 1978 Winterland -Radio-, January 10, 1978/January 14, 1978; ID: 213.0350 (Box 7, Media ID: 213.0350)
      Side A: God Save the Queen, Wanna Belle, Seventeen, NY, EMI, Bodies, Belsen was a Gas, Holidays in the Sun, No Feelings, Problems, Prett Vacant
      Side B: Anarchy in the USA, No Fun, God Save the Queen, Wanna Be Me, Seventeen, NY, EMI, Belson was a Gas, Bodies
    - De La Soul - Buhloone Mindstate/ Gumbo - Dropping Soulful, undated; ID: 213.0351 (Box 7, Media ID: 213.0351)
      Side A: "De La Soul Buhloone Mind State"
      Side B: "Gumbo"
    - Pistols - The Feelies Dec 14, 1977 CBGB, undated; ID: 213.0352 (Box 7, Media ID: 213.0352)
      Contents
      Side A: Anarchy, Seventeen, N.Y., Steppin Stone, Satellite Submission, Liar, No Feeling, Substitute, Pretty Vacant, Problems, No Fun
      Side B: No Fun, Substitute, Pretty Vacant, Problems, Did You, No Wrong, Pushin Shovin, Seventeen, Sid on Trial
    - Sex Pistols - Atlanta 1/5/78, January 5, 1978; ID: 213.0353 (Box 7, Media ID: 213.0353)
      Side A: God Save the Queen, I Wanna Be Me, Seventeen (I'm a Lazy Sod), New York, Bodies, Submission, Holidays in the Sun
      Side B: EMI, No Feelings, Problems, Pretty Vacant, Anarchy in the UK/+ Iggy Stooge: TV Eye/I Feel Alright!!
    - Feelies Max's (one set) 21 May/CBGB (late show) 2 July 1978, May 21, 1978/July 2, 1978; ID: 213.0402 (Box 7, Media ID: 213.0402)
      Side A: Boy Next Door, Fa Ce La, Loveless Love, Fever, Work, Original Love, Crazy, Moscow Nights
      Side B: Boy, Fa Ce La, Moscow Nights, Work, Loveless Love, Clean Girl$, Raised, Crazy Rhythms
    - Hell, CBGB, Thursday Late June 21st '79 Master/ Feelies, Club 57 June 23 '79 Copy, June 21, 1979/June 23, 1979; ID: 213.0403 (Box 7, Media ID: 213.0403)
      Side A: Kid, Crack of Dawn, I Live My Life, I'm Goin, Crosstown Traffic, Lowest Common Denominator, Ignore That Door
      Side B: unknown
    - The Feelies 6.14.78 Max's, June 14, 1978; ID: 213.0404 (Box 7, Media ID: 213.0404)
      Side A: Boy Next Door, Moscow Nights, Work, Loveless Love, Clean Girl, Original Love, Raised Eyebrows, Crazy Rhythms
      Side B: Boy Next Door, Fa Ce La, Mosow Nights, Work, Raised Eyebrows, Crazy Rhythms, Lookin at You
    - Feelies Hurrah March 15, '79/Happy Spring March 21st '79 CBGB, March 15, 1979/March 21, 1979; ID: 213.0405 (Box 7, Media ID: 213.0405)
      Side A: Boy, Original Love, Work, Fa Ce La, Moscow Nights, Raised Eyebrows, Crazy Rhythm, I'm a Believer, Lookin at You
      Side B: Boy, Original Love, Work, Loveless Love, Fa Ce La, Moscow Nights, Raised Eyebrows -->Crazy Rhythms, I'm a Believer
    - Feelies CBGB 22 July '78, July 22, 1978; ID: 213.0406 (Box 7, Media ID: 213.0406)
      Side A: Boy, Fa Ce La, Moscow Nights, Work, Original Love, Raised Eyebrows, Crazy Rhythms
      Side B: Boy, Fa Ce La, Moscow Nights, Work, Loveless Love (crossed out), Clean Girl, Original Love, Raised Eye--> Crazy, Looking at You
      Container Annotation: Greg Delazio - percussion
    - Slits, Irving Plaza Club 57, Nov 15th 1980, November 15, 1980; ID: 213.0267 (Box 7, Media ID: 213.0267)
      Side A: Newtown, Walkabout, Grapevine, Life on Earth, Man Next Door, Typical Girls, Fade Away, Animal Space.
      Side B: Silence is a Rhythm, Shake
    - Iggy My Father's Place Nov. 4, 1979;John Cale Sabotage/Live, ID: 213.0407 (Box 7, Media ID: 213.0407)
      Side A: Real Cool Time, [Track Unknown], I'm Loose, Dogfood, New Valves, T.V. Eye, Sixteen, Your Pretty Face, Play It Safe, Funtime, Be Your Dog-->
      Side B: (Cont'd), China Girl/ Cale: Mercenaries (Ready For War), Baby You Know, Evidence, Dr. Mudd, Only Time Will Tell, Sabotage
    - Iggy & the Stooges, 1969; ID: 213.0408 (Box 7, Media ID: 213.0408)
      Side A: I Wanna Be Your Dog, No Fun, Real Cool Time, Not Right, Little Doll, Down on the Street, Loose, T.V. Eye, Dirt, 1970
      Side B: Funhouse, Search & Destroy, Your Pretty Face is Going to Hell, Raw Power, Shake Appeal, Death Trip
    - Iggy Pop Live March 18th 1977, March 18, 1977; ID: 213.0409 (Box 7, Media ID: 213.0409)
      Side A: Raw Power, T.V. Eye, Dirt, 1969, Turn Blue, Funtime, Gimmie Danger, No Fun, Search & Destroy, I Wanna Be Your Dog
      Side B: Tonight, Some Weird Sin, China Girl
      Container Annotation: Iggy w/ P.S. Group - 96 Tears
    - The Feelies Dec 14, 1977 CBGB, December 14, 1977; ID: 213.0410 (Box 7, Media ID: 213.0410)
      Side A: Real Cool Time, Boy Next Door, Fa Ce La, Clean Girl, Work, [Track Unknown], Little Red Book, Moscow Night, Crazy Rhythms
      Side B: Boy Next Door, Original Love/Sin, Third Uncle, The Thin Line, [Track Unknown], Work, Moscow Night, Slippin
    - Some Jams NYC 78 Speed, 1978; ID: 213.0411 (Box 7, Media ID: 213.0411)
      Side A: Jam: Richard Lloyd and the Feelies Max's Kansas City NYC / 19 Jan 78 Side 1 of 2 (45:54)
      Side B: Side 2 of 2 Patti Smith Group, Richard Lloyd, Richard Hell "My Generation" CBGBs II / NYC 31 Dec 77, 1 Jan 78 (8:52)// Hurram Jam / Hurrahs NYC / 4 Sept 78 John Cale, Chris Spedding, T. Taliafero Drummer (20:47)
      Container Annotation: © Performances and All Original Material Copyright 1978 By the Artists. All Commercial Rights Retained
    - Richard & Linda Thompson Sept 7th Round House London, undated; ID: 213.0412 (Box 7, Media ID: 213.0412)
      Contents: (Original text crossed out, See Container Annotation for Original Text)
      Side A: I Want to See the Bright Lites T'Nite+, Hard Luck Stories(), My Dreams Have Withered and Died*, Streets of Paradise(), Old Woman Tossed Up in a Blanket/Shepards Hey/Bean Setting/Shooting[], A Heart Needs a Home*, Together Again, Everything You Do*
      Side B: Jet Plane in a Rocking Chair(), Never Again*, For Shame of Doing Wrong(), Hokey Pokey+, Looking for You*/Steeleye Span (T.V.) Ballad of Robin Hood, One Misty Musty Morn, Spotted Cow
      Note: () - From "Pour Down Like Silver"; * - NOT SURE; + - TITLE SONGS FROM 1st and 2nd Album; []Medley from "Morrison";- Buck Owens Tune. Drums - Davis [Maptaoks]; Bass - Pat Donaldson; J- Kirkpatrick
      Container Annotation: Advertising Age 7th Annual Idea Workshop Consumer Direct Mail
    - Iggy Pop Oct 31, '79 Palladium, October 31, 1979; ID: 213.0414 (Box 7, Media ID: 213.0414)
      Side A: Real Cool Time, [Track Unknown], I'm Loose, Dog Food, New Values, T.V. Eye, Sixteen, Pretty Face Going to Hell, Play It Safe
      Side B: Funtime, [Track Unknown], I Wanna Be Your Dog, China Girl, One For My Baby An' One Forthe Road, No Fun, Five Foot One, [Track Unknown]